(Sheldon:)The entrance to the dungeon
is a moss-covered door.
(Sheldon:)You manage to open it
only to find yourseIf face-to-face...
(Sheldon:)...with a hideous,
foul-smelling, moss-covered ogre.
(Sheldon:)What do you do?
I say, "Hey, Ma, what's for dinner?"
(Sheldon:)Seventeen.
(Sheldon:)The ogre is amused by your joke
and allows you to pass.
(Sheldon:)By the by, I liked it too.
(Leonard:)How go the wedding plans, Howard?
Great. Spent five hours last night
at Macy's registering for gifts.
I'm finally gonna have that earthenware
asparagus dish I've always wanted, heh.
(Leonard:)See, this is the good thing about
having a girIfriend 9000 miles away.
(Leonard:)I can spend my nights
doing whatever I want.
(Howard:)Like playing nerd games with us...
(Howard:)...and then taking
a suspiciously long shower?
(Leonard:)Maybe.
(Leonard:)We enter the dungeon.